Guide to the Fashion Moda Archive MSS.091
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Fashion Moda as a Business
  - Subseries B: Grants and Fundraising
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal, 1979-1980; cuid8916 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal, 1985-1986; cuid8917 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal, 1988-1989; cuid8918 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal receipts, 1988-1989; cuid8919 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal, 1989-1990; cuid8920 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, proposal, 1990-1991; cuid8921 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, report, 1983-1984; cuid8922 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Funding research., undated; cuid8923 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Fundraising, 1979-1980; cuid8924 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Funds received, 1980-1984; cuid8925 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - H. U. D., fix-up money, 1985; cuid8926 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Institute of Museum services, application, 1980; cuid8927 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Kresge Foundation, grant, 1991; cuid8928 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Media Bureau, the Kitchen Center, application, 1979; cuid8929 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - N. E. A., contract, 1985-1986; cuid8930 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - N. E. A., expansion arts, 1982-1983; cuid8931 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - N. E. A., expansion arts, 1986-1987; cuid8932 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - N. E. A., final reports, 1985-1989; cuid8933 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - N. E. A., interarts "presenting", 1985; cuid8934 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - N. E. A., interarts, 1986-1987; cuid8935 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - N. E. A., interarts, 1987-1988; cuid8936 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - N. E. A., arts (radio), 1984-1985; cuid8937 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - N. E. A., media arts, 1987-1986; cuid8938 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - N. E. A., museum, 1991-1992; cuid8939 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - N. E. A., organization, 1980-1981; cuid8940 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - N. E. A., organization, 1988-1989; cuid8941 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - N. E. A., panel notes, 1986-1988; cuid8942 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - N. E. A., printed material, 1987; cuid8943 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - N. E. A., special exhibitions, 1984-1985; cuid8944 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1980-1981; cuid8945 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1981-1982; cuid8946 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1982-1983; cuid8947 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1983-1984; cuid8948 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1984-1985; cuid8949 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1985-1986; cuid8950 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1985-1988; cuid8951 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1990-1991; cuid8952 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - N. Y. Foundation for the Arts, 1985-1987; cuid8953 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - NYSCA, application, 1984-1985; cuid8954 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - NYSCA, application, 1985-1986; cuid8955 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - NYSCA, application, 1986-1987; cuid8956 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - NYSCA, application, 1987-1988; cuid8957 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - NYSCA, application, 1989-1990; cuid8958 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - NYSCA, application, 1990-1991; cuid8959 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - NYSCA, application, 1991-1992; cuid8960 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - NYSCA, application, 1992-1993; cuid8961 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - NYSCA, application, 1993-1994; cuid8962 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - NYSCA, architectural application, 1990-1991; cuid8963 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - NYSCA, audit, 1989-1991; cuid8964 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1979-1980; cuid8965 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1980-1981; cuid8966 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1981-1982; cuid8967 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1982-1983; cuid8968 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1983-1984; cuid8969 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1985-1986; cuid8970 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1987-1988; cuid8971 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - NYSCA, final report, 1984; cuid8972 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - NYSCA, final report, 1985-1986; cuid8973 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - NYSCA, final report, 1986-1987; cuid8974 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - NYSCA, funded presenters, 1986-1987; cuid8975 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - NYSCA, funding report, 1985-1986; cuid8976 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - NYSCA, slide scripts., undated; cuid8977 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - NYSCA, South Bronx Show proposal, 1987-1988; cuid8978 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - NYSCA: special arts, Marion Brown, 1987; cuid8979 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - NYSCA: special arts, Ken Garrett, 1987-1988; cuid8980 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - NYSCA: special arts, Barbara T. Smith, 1987-1988; cuid8981 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, David Finn, April - May 1984., cuid8982 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, Nan Goldin, August 1983 - July 1984., 1983 - 1984; cuid8983 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, Charles Hardgrove, March 1-30, 1984., cuid8984 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, Dragon Ilic, September 7-30, 1984., cuid8985 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project funding, 1983- 1984; cuid8986 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Presenting new writers, 1987; cuid8987 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Responsibilities of a Director of a New York, New Jersey, or Connecticut Non-Profit Corporation., undated; cuid8988 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Reed Foundation, Inc., 1986; cuid8989 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - South Bronx Cultural Center, 1979- 1980; cuid8990 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Unidentified slide scripts., undated; cuid8991 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Unidentified grant information., undated; cuid8992 (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and Related Material
  Series III is divided into seven subseries and contains 18 boxes of documents. The files are arranged alphabetically and chronologically.
  - Subseries A: Artists Files
    Series III subseries A, Artists Files, contains files Fashion Moda kept on their artists and exhibitions including: resumes, exhibition proposals, plans for exhibitions, consignment forms, program reports, and production materials for exhibitions. Please note that not all of the artists included here actually showed at Fashion Moda.
    - Access Bronx., undated; cuid8993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - African Caribbean poetry theater, June 27, 1987., cuid8994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Agent, announcement., undated; cuid8995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Intentionally omitted, undated; cuid8996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - American Dreaming, December 13 - January 21, 1987., cuid8997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Andreu, Jose: slides, resume., undated; cuid8998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Aone, Toxic, Koor: exhibition, May 1985., cuid8999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Appropriate Technology Project [see also I. 1. 13], undated; cuid9000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Appropriate Technology Project: related newpaper clippings., undated; cuid9001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Art et Industrie: contract, October 16, 1986., cuid9002 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Art for Money Benefit: collecters, December 4, 1986., cuid9003 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Art for Money Benefit: consignment agreements, November - December 1986., cuid9004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Art for Money Benefit: correspondence, receipts, and notes, November - December 1986., cuid9005 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Art for Money Benefit: price list, November - December 1986 [see also I. 1. 33], cuid9006 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Art Womb., undated; cuid9007 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Artist in residence program., undated; cuid9008 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Artists resumes /Chalfant, Henry, undated; cuid9009 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Barbican Arts Group: proposal, 1985; cuid9010 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Brenner, Leslie: proposal., undated; cuid9011 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Brown, Marion: newspaper article, flyer., undated; cuid9012 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Chaiklin, Amy: consignment sheet., undated; cuid9013 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Charles, Andre Pierre: resume, slides, undated; cuid9014 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Intentionally omitted, undated; cuid9015 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Cole, Richard: resume., undated; cuid9016 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Conde, Richard: resume., undated; cuid9017 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Corn, Thom: resume., undated; cuid9018 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Cosentino, Steven: slides, resume., undated; cuid9019 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Cummings, Michael: exhibition proposal., undated; cuid9020 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Danceteria, 1985; cuid9021 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Dawson, Morris: resume., undated; cuid9022 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - De Braud, Alberto: resume., undated; cuid9023 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - [Removed to Oversize], undated; cuid9024 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Dos Santos, Judith: slides, resume., undated; cuid9025 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Dragan Ilic: resume., undated; cuid9026 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - East Village Ladies Salute the Bronx: exhibition, October 24, 1986; cuid9027 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Eins, Stefan: resume, reviews, others 1986. [see also over oversize, box 22, also I. 1. 20 and III. A. 4. 75 and 75A], cuid9028 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Eins, Stefan: notes on Moda, January 1986., cuid9029 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Eins, Stefan: exhibition posters, see oversize box 22, undated; cuid9030 (Box 4, Folder 37A)
    - English, Ron: resume, articles., undated; cuid9031 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Evans, Andrea: proposal, 1981. [see also over oversize box 22] and Buczak, Brian, cuid9032 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9033 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Exhibition, 1981 - 1985 [see also 1. 1. 2 and III. A. 5. 90-93, also pages 20-26 of Finding Guide], cuid9034 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Exhibition ideas., undated; cuid9035 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9036 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Fashion Moda philosophy [see also I. 1. 1A], undated; cuid9037 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: artist contracts, November 1 - 16, 1985., cuid9038 (Box 4, Folder 44A)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: artist contracts, November 1 - 16, 1985., cuid9039 (Box 4, Folder 44B)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: notes, misc., November 1 - 16, 1985., cuid9040 (Box 4, Folder 44C)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: price list, press release, insurance., undated; cuid9041 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Fiorucci, group exhibition, undated; cuid9042 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Five Boroughs Performance Festival, 1984; cuid9043 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Garrett, Ken: slides, resume., undated; cuid9044 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Garramone, Richard: slides, resume., undated; cuid9045 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - German artists., undated; cuid9046 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Golden Door project, 1986; cuid9047 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Graham, Robert and Susan Springfield: exhibition, November 30 - December 22, 1985, cuid9048 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Grami Gallery: Bogota, Columbia, 1985; cuid9049 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Graupe-Pillard, Grace: announcements., undated; cuid9050 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Headley, Wendell E.: resume., undated; cuid9051 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Haimsohn, Jane: see III. A. 4. 17, undated; cuid9052 (Box 4, Folder 54A)
    - Hertz, Betti-Sue: announcement., undated; cuid9053 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Hochmuth, Rosemarie: catalog, 1986; cuid9054 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Hsieh, Tehching: proposal, 1985-1986; cuid9055 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Invitational 1986/87: exhibition., 1986-1987; cuid9056 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Jackson, Isaac: problem, 1985; cuid9057 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Januzzi, Angelo: resume, articles., undated; cuid9058 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Jazz series, 1987; cuid9059 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Kahane, Lisa:: many slides in III. F. boxes 7-15 and various in III. C. boxes 5 and 6, 1-54, undated; cuid9060 (Box 4, Folder 61A.)
    - Koor: announcement. {slide at III. A. 4. 36], undated; cuid9061 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Kush & the Nature Theatre of San Francisco: announcement, mailing list, October, 1986; cuid9062 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Kaplan, Karen: resume., undated; cuid9063 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - La Libertad Logico: exhibition, May 17, 1986., cuid9064 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Legiardi-Laura, Roland: proposal., undated; cuid9065 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Lehman College, 1987; cuid9066 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Levy, Judy: slides, resume, 1986; cuid9067 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Live Radio at Fashion Moda, April 14, 1983. [audio cassette], cuid9068 (Box 4, Folder 68a., Cassette 68a., E-records fales_mss091, E-records cuid9068)
      Scope and Contents
      April 14th, 1983 broadcast of Audio Art, in conjunction with the Live Radio at Fashion Moda Audio Art exhibition. The program contains a mix of the artists' tapes submitted to the exhibition. Curator/Producer: Isaac Jackson.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 90 min.
    - Lower Eastside Print Shop., undated; cuid9069 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Lowinger, Leslie: resume., undated; cuid9070 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Mainland Poetry., undated; cuid9071 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Margot, "Images in Cloth"/Leslie Lowinger, April 15 - May 7, 1986., cuid9072 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Matthews, Joan: resume., undated; cuid9073 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Matschiner, Kristl: resume, photographs., undated; cuid9074 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Melamid, Brad: see III. A. 4. 39, undated; cuid9075 (Box 4, Folder 74A.)
    - MC TV Channel J: "Making Coincidences", a TV series by Stefan Eins application, contract, funding, 1984 -1988. [see III. G. 16], cuid9076 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - MC TV Channel J: notes, 1983- 1988; cuid9077 (Box 4, Folder 75a.)
    - Meet the composer., undated; cuid9078 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9079 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Meyer, Richard: slides, undated; cuid9080 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Moda gallery layout, undated; cuid9081 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Moore,Frank: resume, slides, undated; cuid9082 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Mudmen: articles, undated; cuid9083 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Nadel, Jeremy: artist statement, 1987; cuid9084 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Neumann, Dolores: see III. A. 4. 17, undated; cuid9085 (Box 5, Folder 82A.)
    - New improvements, 1985; cuid9086 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9087 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Nichols Mural/Print project, 1985 [see also I. 1. 33]., cuid9088 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Nieves, Hector: photographs., undated; cuid9089 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Owens, A.: artist statement., undated; cuid9090 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Poets and Writers / Baraka, Amiri, undated; cuid9091 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Pollack, Steven: see III. A. 4. 17.., undated; cuid9092 (Box 5, Folder 88A.)
    - Poppitz, James: c. v., letters of recommendation., undated; cuid9093 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Program report/exhibition listing, 1981 - 1982. [see also oversize, box 20], cuid9094 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Program report/exhibition listing, 1983- 1984; cuid9095 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Program report/exhibition listing, 1985- 1986; cuid9096 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Pullen, Don: see III. A. 4. 17, undated; cuid9097 (Box 5, Folder 93A.)
    - Quinn, Barbara: resume., undated; cuid9098 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Recchia, Louis, undated; cuid9099 (Box 5, Folder 94A.)
    - Rehm, Celeste: slides, proposal., undated; cuid9100 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - RenAva: Christmas cards, undated; cuid9101 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Rollins, Tim & KOS exhibition with also Juma Santos "Journey", January 1985., cuid9102 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Rollins, Tim & KOS "The Inferno", South-Bronx, 1983-1984; cuid9103 (Box 5, Folder 97A.)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9104 (Box 5, Folder 98-101)
    - Roloff, Stephen: "The broken Wall, budget., undated; cuid9105 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Ryan, Debra Gilbert: slides, resume, 1985; cuid9106 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Sacchetto, Bruno & Nancy Stout: exhibition, March 18 - April 12, 1986., cuid9107 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - The Salon: announcement mock-ups, 1986; cuid9108 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - The Salon: promotional materials, 1986; cuid9109 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Sanna, Richard & Heidi Staudt: proposal, slides., undated; cuid9110 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9111 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - "Science, Art, Design, Invention, Technology, Fantasy": production material for book, 1984. [see also I. 1. 29A and III. A. oversize box 21. 114], cuid9112 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Schuster, Ilene: resume, catalog., undated; cuid9113 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9114 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Slide scripts., undated; cuid9115 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Smith, Mary Agnes: workshop, 1984; cuid9116 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - South Bronx Show: 6th annual, 1985; cuid9117 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - South Bronx Show: 7th annual, 1986; cuid9118 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - South Bronx Show: 8th annual, 1988; cuid9119 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Spank: artist resume., undated; cuid9120 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Stout, Nancy: announcement, undated; cuid9121 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9122 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - SUNY curate, 1987; cuid9123 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Telacopy, September 26, 1986., cuid9124 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Tierney, Trin: III. A. 4. 17, undated; cuid9125 (Box 5, Folder 121A)
    - Topical Archeology, proposal., undated; cuid9126 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Touring exhibitions., undated; cuid9127 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Vienne in South Bronx, Rosa Hochmuth & Lisi Misena, 1986; cuid9128 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Wahl, Anita: catalogue, undated; cuid9129 (Box 5, Folder 124A.)
    - Wenneberg, Teresa: resume, undated; cuid9130 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Wheeler, Irene: slides, resume, 1986; cuid9131 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Subseries B: Articles, Press Releases, Flyers, and Announcements.
    Series III Subseries B, Articles, Press Releases, Flyers, and Announcements, contains articles, press releases, flyers and announcements for exhibitions at Fashion Moda.
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1979; cuid9132 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1980; cuid9133 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1981. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9134 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1982. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9135 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1983. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9136 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1984; cuid9137 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1985; cuid9138 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1986; cuid9139 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1987; cuid9140 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1988; cuid9141 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1990- 1993; cuid9142 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, n. d. [see also oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9143 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Articles written by Joe Lewis., undated; cuid9144 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Press releases, 1979 - 1983. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9145 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Press releases, 1984- 1988; cuid9146 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Press releases, 1990-1993; cuid9147 (Box 5, Folder 15A)
    - Flyers, 1979. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9148 (Box 5, Folder 16..)
    - Flyers, 1980. [see also oversize, box 21, cuid9149 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Flyers, 1981. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9150 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Flyers, 1982. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22], cuid9151 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Flyers, 1983. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22], cuid9152 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Flyers, 1984. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22], cuid9153 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Flyers, 1985/1986 [see also oversize, box 21 & 22], cuid9154 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Flyers, 1987. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22], cuid9155 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Flyers, 1988. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9156 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Flyers, 1989 - 1991. [see also oversize, box 21], cuid9157 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Flyers, 1992- 1993; cuid9158 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Flyers, n. d., undated; cuid9159 (Box 5, Folder 26A.)
    - Flyer mockup, undated; cuid9160 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Flyers for other galleries. [see also oversize, box 21], undated; cuid9161 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Show announcements, 1980- 1985; cuid9162 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Show announcements, 1986- 1992; cuid9163 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Show announcements, n. d., undated; cuid9164 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Show announcements for other galleries., undated; cuid9165 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Subseries C: Photographs
    Series III Subseries C, Photographs, contains photographs covering exhibition openings, artworks, artists, Fashion Moda's neighborhood, and performances.
    - Ahearn, John: cast making., undated; cuid9166 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Agent., undated; cuid9167 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Animals Living in the City, Christy Rupp., undated; cuid9168 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Archeology, Liz n' Val, October 26 - November 23, 1991., cuid9169 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Artist collective & community members video, March 10, 1979., cuid9170 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Aspen Colorado Show [see also I. 1. 34], undated; cuid9171 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Brasz, Mark, undated; cuid9172 (Box 6, Folder 6A.)
    - Buggiani, Paolo [see also I. 1. 7], undated; cuid9173 (Box 6, Folder 6B.)
    - California billboards, 1980 - 1981 [see also I. 1. 17 and III. F. 15. slides 36-38], cuid9174 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Camouflaged Panzerism, undated; cuid9175 (Box 6, Folder 7A.)
    - Clark, Elizabeth: "Reconstruction", 1980; cuid9176 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Collins, Marshall: "World of Dinosaur", November 23 & December 6, 1983; cuid9177 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets., undated; cuid9178 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Cooper, Jerome., undated; cuid9179 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Daze, undated; cuid9180 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - De Mille, Arnette, undated; cuid9181 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Dejon, undated; cuid9182 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Dickson, Jane: "City Maze", September 6 - October 4, 1980., cuid9183 (Box 6, Folder 14A)
    - Edwards, Marianne: July, 1980; cuid9184 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Expressions Africans, February, 1987 (?).; cuid9185 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Facade [see also I. 1. 40], undated; cuid9186 (Box 6, Folder 16A.)
    - Fashion Moda T-shirt, undated; cuid9187 (Box 6, Folder 16B.)
    - Fekner, John: "From the Monkey to the Monitor", November 13 - December 4, 1982; cuid9188 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Freedom, undated; cuid9189 (Box 6, Folder 17A.)
    - Fun Shots, undated; cuid9190 (Box 6, Folder 17B)
    - Graffiti Art: Australia, 1987; cuid9191 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Graffiti Exhibition, 1980 [see also I. 1. 15 and III. B. oversize 21. 14-18], cuid9192 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Graffiti Artist's from the Early 70's, May 1984., cuid9193 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Group shot including Brasz, Daze, Easy-G, Eins ,Haring and Headley, 1983; cuid9194 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Holmes, Victor:, 1988; cuid9195 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Holzer, Jenny: facade of Fashion Moda [see also I. 1. 22 and III. A. oversize21. 32B], undated; cuid9196 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Howland, Becky 1981 Image for South Bronx Poster., cuid9197 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Image for South Bronx Poster, undated; cuid9198 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Jones Baird, Stefan Eins, Mark Kostabi, 1985-1986; cuid9199 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - "Ladys Wrestling", June 14, 1980., cuid9200 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Lorenz, Patrice: "From Farrakahn to Fallwell", 1984; cuid9201 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Lubar, Cindy: "119 Comments", 1981., cuid9202 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - [item removed], undated; cuid9203 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Misera, Lisi:, 1991; cuid9204 (Box 6, Folder 30)